[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word \u2018ocean\u2019 is of Greek origin.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other name for the sponge cake called Battenberg cake?", "correct_answer": "Window cake", "incorrect_answers": ["Bathroom cake", "Chair cake", "Door cake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Albuquerque is the largest city of which U.S. state?", "correct_answer": "New Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio", "Kansas", "Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Academy Awards did the 1998 movie Saving Private Ryan not win?", "correct_answer": "Best Picture", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Sound", "Best Director", "Best Editing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sally Field, Shirley MacLaine and Julia Roberts starred in the 1989 movie Fried Green Tomatoes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pitch of the guitar string becomes lower when it is tightened.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the next change in the course of its stellar evolution, what is the Sun expected to evolve into?", "correct_answer": "Red giant", "incorrect_answers": ["Black hole", "Supernova", "White dwarf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ludwig van Beethoven included the Italian phrase, Quasi una fantasia in the title of his Piano Sonata No. 14, popularly known as the Moonlight Sonata. What does this Italian phrase mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Almost a fantasy", "incorrect_answers": ["Just a fantasy", "A pure fantasy", "Reality and fantasy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous car chase sequence takes place on what L.A. freeway, and where did the minor traffic tie-up mentioned by the female traffic reporter occur?", "correct_answer": "710 Northbound, just past Henry Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["118 Westbound, near the San Fernando Rd Exit", "405 Southbound,  just beyond the Century Blvd East Ramp", "101 westbound,  near the 23 Freeway Off Ramp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This vitamin, known as pantothenic acid, is found in some hair and skin care products.", "correct_answer": "B5", "incorrect_answers": ["C", "B12", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Arab-Israeli War in 1973, known as Yom Kippur War, triggered the \u20181973 oil crisis\u2019. What action did the Arab members of OPEC undertake as part of their strategy?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They raised the price of oil", "They proclaimed an embargo on oil exports to the Netherlands", "They proclaimed an embargo on oil exports to the United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What U.S. interstate runs east and west through Colorado?", "correct_answer": "I-70", "incorrect_answers": ["I-40", "I-80", "I-90"]}]